[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to the science (or art) of kissing?", "correct_answer": "Philematology", "incorrect_answers": ["Palilogy", "Phlebology", "Palynology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In astronomy, what is a syzygy?", "correct_answer": "An alignment of 3 celestial bodies", "incorrect_answers": ["A shooting star", "A comet", "An eclipse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a possible cause of sudden-onset shortness of breath?", "correct_answer": "Both of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Neither of these", "Acute myocardial infarction", "Pulmonary embolism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The moon orbits eastward around the Earth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not part of the group of brain-supplying arteries, known as the circle of Willis?", "correct_answer": "basilar artery", "incorrect_answers": ["anterior communication artery", "internal carotid artery", "posterior communication artery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cartoon Great Dane often needs his nephew headstrong nephew to protect him.", "correct_answer": "Scooby", "incorrect_answers": ["Odie", "Scrappy", "Snoopy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term denotes the classification of organisms, based on their evolutionary descent?", "correct_answer": "Phylogenetics", "incorrect_answers": ["Ornithology", "Neuroethology", "Paleontology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of Benjamins kids from the 2000 movie The Patriot?", "correct_answer": "Elizabeth", "incorrect_answers": ["Samuel", "William", "Margaret"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which are the only  two states in the USA that do not allow drivers to pump their own gas?", "correct_answer": "New Jersey and Oregon", "incorrect_answers": ["Utah and Wyoming", "New Jersey and Utah", "Oregon and Wyoming"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where are the origins of the Rhine?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Belgium", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of criminal does Tom Powers become in the 1931 crime movie The Public Enemy?", "correct_answer": "Bootlegger", "incorrect_answers": ["Drug dealer", "Bank robber", "Assassin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what 1999 movie is the quote I see dead people?", "correct_answer": "The Sixth Sense", "incorrect_answers": ["Armageddon", "The Silence of the Lambs", "Psycho"]}]